D.A字幕組&遠鑒字幕組聯合譯制
翻譯：小佩吉環球旅行
校對：死不了的逆閃電
調校：william2568
總監：死不了的逆閃電
樂高DC超級英雄：閃電俠
漂亮
Booyah!
半人 半機器
Half man, half machine.
整個都厲害
All awesome.
我簡直就是忍者遇上游俠
I'm like a ninja meets an acrobat.
我是忍者蝙啊
I'm a ninjabat!
說不定我也是蝙蝠家族中的一員呢
Maybe I'm in the bat family.
夢想果然還是要有的
Dreams do come true.
我實在是……
I am so...
太牛逼了
Amazing.
啊？
Huh?
怎麼也不讓我牛逼一回 是不？
Couldn't let me have it,could you?
你在正義大廳[著名的正義聯盟行動基地]參觀的最後一站就是這裡
And your tour of the Hall of Justice concludes here.
我們特別設計的
In our specially designed
全國最頂級的高精尖訓練設施
state-of-the-art training facility.
原子俠 這位是鋼骨
Atom, meet Cyborg.
機械專家鋼骨
Cyber mechanical specialist
還有我們正義聯盟的陽光小射線
and the League's little ray of sunshine.
嗨 原子俠
Hey, Atom.
啊 家犬亞種
Ah, Canis lupus familiaris.
一個常見的說法認為 狗是人類最好的朋友
It's a common hypothesis that dog is man's best friend.
但是，呃……不是我說的
But, uh... Not mine.
哇哦，酷！哦……
Whoa, cool! Oh...
“原子俠”我明白你的名字是怎麼來的了
"The Atom."I see what you did there
你可以縮小成任何小玩意啊
with your name and you shrinking down all tiny and stuff.
別緊張 原子俠
Relax, Atom.
這是大A，蝙蝠犬
This is Ace, the Bat-Hound.
他只是評估你一下
He's just evaluating you.
根據我的科學評估
Well, in my scientific evaluation,
大A可以說是非常嚇人了
Ace is very intimidating.
可不是嘛
Tell me about it.
跟動物打交道的第一課
Lesson one with animals.
永遠別膽怯
Never show weakness.
夥計 我覺得我得換機油了
Man, I think I need an oil change.
蝙蝠俠，我真不知道你還有一個……
Batman, I didn't know you had a...
呃 超級寵物
Uh... Super-Pet.
大A可不只是一隻寵物
Ace the Bat-Hound is more than a pet.
他是最好的小夥伴
He's the best sidekick
一個穿披風的騎士夢寐以求那種
a caped crusader could ever have.
那羅賓呢？
What about Robin?
你是不是最強夥伴呀？沒錯你就是
Aren't you the best sidekick? Yes, you are, yes you are.
我也好想要蝙蝠俠給我揉揉肚子
Aw, I want a Bat belly rub.
所以 原子俠
So, Atom.
現在正義大廳你也參觀過了……
Now that you've seen the Hall of Justice...
你有什麼想法？
What do you think?
想不想加入正義聯盟？
Would you like to become a member of the Justice League?
我……
I...
等一會兒再回答
Hold your diminutive answer.
跟我來
Follow me.
快點啦 塑膠人 這是麻煩事警報
Come on, Plas,it's the trouble alert.
但是我好餓啊，得有人送我一程
But I'm starving.I need a pick-me-up.
拿這個送你一程怎麼樣？
How's this for a pick-me-up?
一份快餐外賣就能送你好大一程
One order of fast food to give you a boost.
啊？什麼？喂！
Huh? What? Hey!
想當團隊加油員你還差得遠呢 火風暴
Way to be a team motivator, Firestorm.
看看今天是誰需要我們幫助
Let's see who needs our help today.
我是路易絲·萊恩 為大家帶來爆炸性消息
This is Lois Lane with Breaking News.
哥譚市的犯罪王子
Gotham City's clown prince of crime,
小丑 已經侵入了我們摯愛的城市
the Joker, has invaded our beloved city.
啊
Ah.
陽光大都會啊
Sunny Metropolis.
擺脫哥譚黑暗騎士的完美度假勝地
The perfect getaway from Gotham's Dark Knight.
想來一次小小的度假
Nothing like a little vacation
沒什麼比把我的小寵物放在腳底下遛遛更好的了
to put the pep back in my step.
哦我的天吶
Oh, my!
小丑在城市裡大放毒氣
The Joker's gassing the city.
誰能來阻止這個搞破壞的小丑呢？
Who can stop this ruinous jester?
幫幫我們吧！正義聯盟 超人！
Help us!Justice League, Superman.
救救我們！
Save us!
天啊！路易絲遇上麻煩了
Great Scott!Lois is in trouble.
又一次
Again.
好啦隊員們 我們出發吧
All right, team,gear up and let's go.
原子俠 這是你的大好機會
Atom, this is your chance
加入正義聯盟一展身手
to join he Justice League in action.
- 你準備好了嗎？ - 我 呃……
-Are you ready? - I, uh...
不要有壓力
No pressure.
我們明白你是超級英雄裡的新人
We know you're new at being a superhero.
如果你願意的話 你可以留在這裡
If you want, you can stay here
跟大A和克利皮托一起玩一會兒
and hang out with Ace and Krypto.
克利皮托？
Krypto?
還有一隻超級寵物？
Another Super-Pet?
算了 我寧可選小丑也不要狗
Yeah, I'll take the clown over the canine.
越快越好
The sooner, the better.
哦 星球日報的新聞大樓
Ooh, the Daily Planet news building.
唔 導遊管這個叫
Hmm, the visitors' guide calls it
“大都會市天際線的明珠”
"The jewel of the Metropolis skyline."
真沒勁
Meh. Kinda boring.
咱們來翻修一下吧！
Let's renovate!
那小丑真不要臉
The nerve of that clown.
他居然在踐踏我們大都會市天際線的明珠
He's tromping all over the jewel of the Metropolis skyline.
他還亂穿馬路不守交規
And he's jaywalking.
讓我們把他拿下
Let's take him down.
還有歡迎委員會啊？
The welcoming committee.For me?
幸好我帶了奶油小點心
Good thing I brought pastry.
哇哦 那是椰子奶油嗎？
Ooh, is that coconut cream?
是檸檬蛋白酥
Lemon meringue.
帶自爆那種
With a bang.
撐住啊 要撞啦！
Brace for impact!
多麼美麗又安全的公園一日游啊
What a beautiful, perfectly safe day at the park.
早知道我就開自己的隱形飛機了
- I should've taken my jet.- Ooh. Ooh.
我還能挺住
I'm holding it together.
好丟人啊
Oh, this is embarrassing.
也沒那麼好笑吧 考慮下別人的感受好不好
It's not that funny.A little consideration here.
路易絲 鋼骨
Lois, Cyborg.
你倆冷靜點！
Try to stay calm!
我還能聽見！
I can still hear you.
現在這情況屬於正常操作嗎？
Is this normally how it goes?
正常啊 但是一般來說不會笑成這樣
Yeah, but usually with a little less laughter.
這個笑法很危險
That laughter is dangerous.
我們得幫幫這些人
We've gotta help these people
趁他們還沒把自己笑死
before they laugh themselves to death.
而且要在小丑禍害其它人之前阻止他
And stop the Joker before he endangers anyone else.
那我們就分頭行動吧
Then let's divide and conquer.
對 我們得用閃電般的速度把這堆亂攤子清理乾淨
Yup, we'll have this mess cleaned up in a flash.
說到這個 閃電俠哪兒去了？
Speaking of,where is the Flash?
我好幾分鐘以前就把警報發出去了
I sent out the Justice alert minutes ago.
一級警報
Priority one.
巴裡很清楚我對遲到的看法
Barry knows how I feel about tardiness.
快點 巴裡 起床啦
Come on, Barry. Get up.
一下……
And one...
……兩千
And 2,000.
好了 我起來了
Okay, I'm up.
衝個澡
Shower time.
下次真的得記住要等水熱了再進去洗
Whoa, I have got to remember to wait for the water to warm up before jumping in.
不錯
Nice.
好啦中城 讓我們開始派對吧
All right, Central City,let's get this party started.
嘿！你撞了我的車！
Hey, hey, hey, you hit my car!
- 搞成這樣誰來收拾啊？ - 我？明明是你撞我
- Who's gonna take care of this?- Me? You hit me.
我非告得你傾家蕩產不可
I'm gonna sue you for every brick you've got.
謝謝 閃電俠！
Thanks, Flash!
那就是閃電俠
That guy's Flash.
你們好啊 小鳥
Hidey ho, birdies.
哦 小心看路啊 早上好啊 童子軍52號編隊
Ooh, watch your step.Good morning, Troop 52.
哈嘍 熱狗
Hello, hot dog.
不用上學了  不用上學了
- No school.- No way. No school?
喔！多謝了 閃電俠！
Whoa! Thanks, Flash!
謝謝 閃電俠
Thanks, Flash.
謝謝閃電俠！謝謝閃電俠！
- Thanks, Flash!- Thanks, Flash!
哇！
Whoa!
謝啦 閃電俠！
Thanks, Flash!
才起床五分鐘
Five minutes out of bed
就做了這麼多事
and look at all the good I've done.
輪到大都會了
Time to get to Metropolis
來見識一下正義……
to meet up with the Justice...
哦 這個咕嚕咕嚕的聲音我懂
Oh, I know that grumble.
它是在說 甜甜圈 現在！
And it's saying,"Donuts, now!"
最好吃的甜甜圈在哪裡？
And where are the best donuts?
哥譚市
Gotham City.
所有中了毒氣的人都已經安全撤離了
All the victims are safely evacuated.
塑膠人
Plastic Man,
你也中了小丑的毒氣了嗎？
were you infected by Joker's gas?
沒有 都是因為他們笑的那樣兒 太搞笑了
No, it's all this laughing.It's hilarious.
救我！
Help me!
塑膠 嚴肅點
Plas, get serious,
我們必須找到治好這些市民的方法
we have to find a cure for these civilians.
我覺得如果我能改變小丑毒氣的分子結構
I wonder if I can alter the molecular structure of Joker's gas
就能造出解毒劑
to create a cure.
- 怎麼做？ - 在這等著
- How?- Wait here.
好的
Okay.
假設
Hypothesis.
以這個大小我應該就能找到小丑毒氣中
At this size I should be able to find trace elements
飄浮在這個地區空氣中的微量元素
of Joker's gas still wafting around the area.
啊哈！
Aha!
一個小丑毒氣分子
A Joker gas molecule.
找到這個沒啥好玩的
There's nothing funny about this.
現在來做個小小的實驗
Now for a little experiment.
他在那兒呢 讓我來揍扁這個小丑
- There he is.- I've got this clown.
永遠不要低估小丑的實力 火風暴
Never underestimate the Joker, Firestorm.
我繞到他背後去 然後我們用……
I'll fly around behind him and then we'll take him by...
啊？
Huh?
驚不驚喜？
Surprise?
這下慘了 老兄
Not cool, man.
蝙蝠俠會讓我把這個糗事記一輩子的
Batman will never let me live this down.
是誰總是逗我樂啊
Whoo hoos always bring a smile to my face.
你得比那個快才能
You've got to be faster than that
偷偷潛入小丑身邊
to sneak up on the Joker.
閃電俠去哪兒了？
Where is Flash?
那是閃電俠！
It's the Flash!
天底下最好吃的甜甜圈
Best donut ever.
甜甜圈安全！
Saved the donut.
那誰來救你啊
But who's gonna save you?
冰凍隊長？
Captain Cold?
我今天唯一感興趣的霜就是這塊甜甜圈上的糖霜
The only frosting I'm interested in today is on this donut.
馬上投降的話 我們就把今天這事當成是
Give up now and we'll chalk it up
全球變暖的禍
to hysteria over global warming.
才不是 今天是全球冷凍的禍
Instead, let's chalk it up to global freezing.
全球冷凍？那根本都不是個正經詞兒好吧
"Global freezing"?That doesn't even make sense.
拜託 你可比這個要有料一點
Come on, Cold, you got better material than that.
就叫“零度以下的飛來橫禍”怎麼樣？
How about, "Chances of that are below zero?"
唉 算了
Ah, never mind.
我能看出來我講的這個冷笑話把你冷到了
I can see my puns leave you cold.
冷啊
Cold.
他隨你處置了 警官
He's all yours, Officer.
現在是時候去大都會了
Now it's off to Metropolis.
多謝了 閃電俠
Thanks, Flash!
嗨 你知道這些甜甜圈配啥最好不？
Hey, you know what goes good with those donuts?
你去沒去過那個
You ever been to that
在星城的蘭伯特奶昔？
Lampert's Milkshakes in Star City?
沒
No.
準備 瞄準…
Ready, aim...
發射！
Fire!
這些機器小丑速度好快
These roboclowns are quick.
每次我來城裡觀光
Whenever I visit the city,
最喜歡的就是看一場好的演出
I just love to take in a good show.
那你肯定會喜歡我的表演
Then you're gonna love my performance as
我演直升機
a helicopter.
乾得好，塑膠人
Well done, Plas.
真棒！好精彩的表演
Bravo! Wonderful performances.
我笑了 我哭了
I laughed, I cried.
我的機器小丑都死了
My roboclowns died.
給你最熱烈的粉絲拍張照如何？
Photo for your biggest fan?
茄子
Say, "Cheese."
塑膠人 不要！
Plas, no!
這就是書裡那種最老的惡作劇對吧？
That was the oldest trick in the book, wasn't it?
你這傢伙的腦子真是慢得可以
You are so gonna get it later.
我愛死他們高空摔落地面成就經典這一幕了
I love it when they fall for the classics.
哦 塑膠人
Oh, Plastic Man!
聰明倒是挺聰明，可惜腦子老是慢半拍
Always clever,but never too quick.
閃電俠
Flash.
哇哦
Wow.
我想說 真的是 哇哦
I mean, really, wow.
蝙蝠俠肯定要氣炸了 他最討厭遲到
Batman is gonna be so mad.He hates tardiness.
哦，追逐戲，我最愛追逐戲碼了
Ooh, a chase scene.I love chase scenes.
迴旋鏢隊長
Captain Boomerang.
你知道嗎，你是我今天碰到的第二個
You know, you're the second captain wearing blue
穿藍衣服的隊長了
that I've run into today.
你們是組了個俱樂部還是怎麼樣？
You guys have a club or something?
那是 俱樂部名字叫“乾翻閃電俠”
Yeah, it's the"Let's destroy Flash" club.
呃……哦
Uh-oh.
又一發 再來一發
And another, and another.
還有一發
And another.
哈！沒打著！
Ha! Missed me!
- 哦 真的嗎？ - 是的
- Oh, did I?- Yeah, you did.
哎呀！
Crikey!
這下迴旋鏢可迴旋不動了
Well, that puts the boom in Boomerang.
啊？
Huh?
我錯過麻煩事警報了
I missed the trouble alert.
我的錯 調成震動了
My bad, had it on vibrate.
蝙蝠俠肯定氣瘋了
Batman is gonna be so mad.
哎呀！奶昔不錯嘛
Blimey! Good shake.
注意了 大都會旅遊協會
Attention,Metropolis Board of Tourism,
你們的旅遊搞得我好無聊
I'm bored with your tourism.
奇思妙想在哪裡？哪裡好玩啦？
Where's the whimsy,where's the fun?
哼 我現在就給你們弄點好玩的
Well, I'm gonna give it to ya
看我的好玩加農炮
with my Fun Cannon.
終於，
At last,
我最大的敵人打出了他最後一張牌
my greatest foe plays his final card.
只有我一個人能阻止他
And it's up to me alone to stop him.
這將是我們的終極之戰
This could be our end game.
這是最後的戰役 在一段很長的……
The last battle in a long...
不好 他的武器充能好快
Impressive, his weapon charged so quickly.
他要按按鈕了 沒時間了 必須馬上出擊
He's going for the trigger. No time.Have to strike now, go!
小蝠蝠 在哥譚市裡我最想念的人就是你啦
Batsy, how I've missed you in Gotham City.
但你現在總是跟你的朋友們一起行動了
You're always off to play with your superfriends now.
所以我大老遠跑到大都會來跟你們一起好好玩玩
So I came all the way to Metropolis to join the fun.
好玩的都玩完了 小丑
Fun's over, Joker.
我已經阻止了你的計劃
I foiled your plan.
什麼？哦···
What? Oh.
你以為你的蝙蝠鏢已經擊潰了我的好玩加農炮了嗎？
You thought your Batarang defeated my Fun Cannon?
等下 你那個按鈕是幹啥用的？
Wait, then what's that button for?
這個鈕嗎？
This button?
這是空調開關
It turns on the air conditioner.
這個按鈕才是我的好玩加農炮開炮用的
This button fires my Fun Cannon.
不！
No!
太慢了 小蝠蝠
Too slow, Batsy.
現在這情況看起來可不太妙
This does not look good.
你說得對
You're right.
這個看起來簡直要笑死人了
It looks hilarious.
謝謝 謝謝大家 我會在這裡表演整整一周的
Thank you, thank you.I'll be here all week.
實際上 我覺得我可以在這呆一輩子
In fact, I think I'll stay here forever!
現在 如果我把這個原子
Now, if I just add this atom
加在這個分子上
on to this molecule,
它應該能讓毒氣失效
it should make the gas inert.
搞定了！我剛剛發現了解藥
Eureka!I've discovered the cure.
現在，合成一個疫苗
Now, to synthesize a vaccine.
我說……
I said...
蝙蝠小丑？
Batclown?
呃 我活已經幹完了
Well, my work is done here.
啊？
Huh?
抱歉我來晚了
Sorry I'm late.
他打敗了小丑 謝謝你！
He took down the Joker! Thank you!
什麼？
What?
謝謝 謝謝大家
Thank you, thank you.
你知道 這點活一天就搞定了
You know,it's all in a day's work.
喔哦 你怎麼搞成這樣？
Whoa! What happened to you?
你遲到的時候就會搞成這樣！
This is what happens when you're late!
我知道 非常抱歉
I know, I am so sorry.
因為我把我的聯盟警報器調到振動模式了
I had my League alert on vibrate.
然後我這一早上特別忙 又是冰凍隊長又是迴旋鏢隊長的
And then a really busy morning with Captain Cold and Captain Boomerang.
但是 嗨 我們抓到小丑了
But, hey,the Joker is captured
然後大家從衣著來看都沒什麼不好的地方
and everyone seems no worse for wear.
- 啊 大部分吧  - 還有星球日報
- Well, mostly...- And the Daily Planet?
什麼？
What?
終極大樓變身準備 三 二  一！
Extreme building makeover in three, two, one!
萬歲！閃電俠最棒了！
- Hurray!- Flash is the best.
超級速度啥都能修復 跟新的一樣
Super speed fixes everything.Just like new.
你想不想讓我把你也修復一下呀 蝙蝠俠？
You want me to fix you up, too, Batman?
不是啥都都能用超級速度來修復的
Not everything can be fixed with speed.
閃電俠 蝙蝠俠想說的是
Flash, what Batman is trying to say,
我們都是你的朋友
is that we're you're friends.
我沒想說這個
That's not what I said.
我們想讓你成為你能做到的最好的英雄
And we want you to be the best hero you can be.
有時候那意味著放慢速度
Sometimes that means slowing down.
留意一下你的周圍
Being aware of your surroundings.
而且永遠有一套計劃
And always having a plan.
- 閃電俠？ - 慢下來
- Flash?- Slow down.
環境還有計劃 記下了
Surroundings and plan, got it.
- 話題標籤 #前瞻性行動#…… - 閃電俠？
- Hashtag proactive.- Flash?
更新我的英雄熱線 英雄Ins[Ins：美國社交網站、應用]
Updating my Hero Hotline, Herogram.
愛英雄，英雄烏托邦和我的英雄
I-Hero, Herotopia and MyHero
推送一下我打敗小丑的消息
with my takedown of the Joker.
哦 太感謝你們了 正義聯盟
Oh, thank you, Justice League.
沒有你們我們真不知道該怎麼辦
We don't know what we'd do without you.
- 嗯……- 嗯 市長 只要我是世界上速度最快的人
- Well...- Well, Mayor, as long as I'm the fastest man alive,
那你永遠都不用擔心
you'll never have to worry about it.
但你才不是世界上速度最快的人
But you aren't the fastest man alive.
你是個騙子
You're a fraud,
就像正義聯盟的其它成員一樣
just like the rest of the Justice League.
世界很快就會發現這一點
Something the world will see soon enough.
- 那個人是誰啊 - 不知道
- Who was that?- No clue.
我會把他找出來的
But I'm gonna find out.
閃電俠 等等
Flash, wait.
這傢伙速度還真快
Huh? This guy is seriously fast.
你穿的是鐵靴子嗎？
Are you wearing iron boots?
我知道你動作會慢一些，
I knew you would be slow,
但我還真不知道你會慢成這樣
but I didn't know you'd be this slow.
你才不可能打敗我
No way you're beating me.
這倒挺新鮮
Whoa! That's new.
哇！
Wow!
我在哪兒？
Where am I?
別急 你會再看見的
Don't worry,you'll see it again.
很快
Soon.
似曾相識啊
Deja vu. Bah.
下一次可得記住
You'd think I'd learn by now.
不錯
Nice.
哦耶 是時候出發了！
Oh, yeah. It's go time!
- 嘿！你撞我車了！- 什麼？根本不能怪我 你看看我的車
- Hey, you hit my car!- What? That ain't my fault, look at my car.
哥們兒 我們昨天就來過一遍了
Guys, we did this yesterday,
你倆開車真該仔細看看路
you really gotta watch where you're going.
謝謝 閃電俠
Thanks, Flash.
不用上學了 不用上學了
- No school.- No way. No school?
連續兩天爆胎？
Two blowouts in a row?
聽著 這是城市那邊我相熟的一家輪胎店
Listen, here's the card for a tire shop I know across town.
如果你提我名字的話他們會以超優惠的價格給你換新輪胎的
They'll give you a great deal on new tires if you mention my name.
拜拜
- See ya.- Uh...
謝謝 閃電俠
Thanks, Flash?
Thanks, Flash.
喔啊！
Whoa!
哈 你知道不 跟昨天我們搭的那個比
Ha! You know, I like this one even better than the one
我更喜歡今天搭的這個
we put up yesterday.
謝啦 閃電俠！
Thanks, Flash!
三重似曾相識
Triple deja vu.
餓了
Oh, hungry.
你知道有啥東西能讓我的肚子感覺好一點不？
You know what would make my tummy feel better?
再來一輪福克斯家的甜甜圈
Another round of donuts at Fox's
而且這次我不用再操心
and this time I won't have to worry about
冰凍隊長耽誤我吃飯了
Captain Cold interrupting my chowtime.
是閃電俠 哦！
- It's the Flash.- Ooh!
最好吃的甜甜圈……
Best donut ever...
呃 真的假的？
Ugh. Seriously?
你不可能把這套再搞一遍吧
There's no way this is happening again.
這是“全球冷凍”的禍！
Chalk it up to global freezing!
- 哎 你現在是在重複自己 - 不是 我才沒有！
- Well, now you're just repeating yourself.- No, I'm not!
你有 你昨天跟我說的是一模一樣的話
Yeah, you said the same thing to me yesterday.
昨天？
Yesterday?
昨天我還在家裡計劃這次搶劫呢
Yesterday I was at home planning this heist.
看起來你是腦殼被凍壞了
It looks like you might be suffering from some brain freeze.
我……
I...
我甚至都還沒回過神兒來
I don't even have a comeback for this,
這也太詭異了
this is just too weird.
好吧 再來一遍 像這樣
Okay, one more time,like this.
那個放那兒 你往這邊走
Put that there,you go over here.
我就不擋在路中間了
And I step out of the way.
他歸你處置了 警官
He's all yours, Officers.
這回 想辦法把這傢伙關進監獄 行不？
This time, try to keep him in prison, would you?
嗨 閃電俠 你知道用啥搭配這些甜甜圈最好嗎？
Hey, Flash, you know what goes good with those donuts?
星城的蘭伯特奶昔？
Lampert's Milkshakes in Star City?
哦 你去過了？
Oh, you've been there?
是啊 非常確定
Yeah, pretty sure.
還是同一輛車
That's the same car.
有些真的很奇怪的事正在發生
Something seriously strange is going on.
我必須得趕到大都會去了
I have gotta get to Metropolis.
幫我拿著這個
Hold this for me.
啊？
Huh?
謝啦 閃電俠
Thanks, Flash.
這一天整的
What a day.
好玩的都玩完了 我阻止了你的邪惡計劃
Fun's over,I foiled your plan.
什麼？
What?
哦 你以為你的蝙蝠鏢擊潰了我的好玩加農炮嗎？
Oh, you thought your Batarang defeated my Fun Cannon?
等下 那個按鈕是幹啥用的？
Wait, then what's that button for?
這個按鈕嗎？
This button?
這是空調開關
It turns on the air conditioner.
這個按鈕才是我的好玩加農炮的開炮按鈕
This button fires my Fun Cannon.
- 什麼？- 找這個嗎？
- Huh?- Looking for this?
哎呀 看起來好痛
Ow, that looked painful.
你來晚了
You're late.
我還希望你說句“謝啦 閃電俠”呢
I was hoping for a,"Thanks, Flash."
假期結束
Vacation's over.
我連個馬戲團都還沒看到
And I didn't even get a tan.
哦 天 諸位 我剛度過了人生中最詭異的一天
Oh, man, guys, I have had the weirdest day.
感覺好像我做的一切事情都是昨天的重複
It's like everything I did yesterday is repeating itself.
除了現在 因為我昨天趕到這的時候，
Except right now, because when I got here yesterday,
星球日報大廈已經被“小丑化”了
the Daily Planet had been Joker-fied
而且蝙蝠俠還穿得像個小丑一樣
and Batman was dressed like a clown.
非常不可能
Highly unlikely.
閃電俠 你今天的遲到
Flash, your tardiness today
將這座城市和整個聯盟都置於危險之中 你得……
endangered this city
and the League. You need to...
放慢速度 留心周圍的人和事 準備一套計劃
Slow down, be aware of my surroundings and have a plan.
一點兒也……等一下 我有沒有……
Exact... Wait a minute.Have I...
說過一樣的話？沒錯，昨天剛說的
Given the speech before?Yes, yesterday.
- 感覺就像…… - 似曾相識？
- Which feels like...- Deja vu?
你 是你幹的！
You! You did this!
我不太確定你都乾了些啥 但是我知道這肯定都怪你
I'm not sure what you did,but I know it's your fault.
- 那個人是誰啊 - 不知道
- Who was that?- No clue.
- 但是我會把他找出來的 - 閃電俠 等一下
- But I'm gonna find out.- Flash, wait!
還是不夠快哦
Still not fast enough.
這回你可跑不了了
You are not getting away this time.
你抓不到我的
You can't catch me.
也許你昨天運氣還好些
Maybe you'll have better luck yesterday.
哦 天吶
Oh, man.
我的似曾相識感覺似曾相識啊
My deja vu is having deja vu.
謝啦，閃電俠
Thanks, Flash!
Thanks, Flash.
謝啦，閃電俠
這一天過的
What a day.
是麻煩事兒警報
It's the trouble alert!
我們來看看今天有誰需要我們幫助
Let's see
who needs our help today.
這裡是路易絲·萊恩 為您帶來爆炸性新聞
This is Lois Lane with Breaking News.
哥譚市的犯罪王子 小丑
Gotham City's clown prince of crime, the Joker,
正在入侵我們摯愛的城市
was invading our beloved city,
- 但是他突然消失了- 什麼？
- but he suddenly vanished.- Huh?
你的麻煩事兒警報總是這麼不麻煩的嗎？
Is your trouble alert always this not troubling?
各位！
Guys!
聽著 我阻止了小丑 但是聽著啊
Look, I stopped the Joker,but listen.
我現在有個更大的麻煩
I've got an even bigger problem.
是啊 你的褲子
Great Scott, you're right.Your pants!
- 沒了 - 什麼？
- They're gone.- Huh?
看起來你是沒褲子穿了
Looks like you ran out of pants.
閃電俠是正義聯盟的正式成員嗎？
So is Flash actually in the League,
還是類似於榮譽成員？
or just, like,an honorary member?
怪不得腿涼
Well, that explains the draft.
聽著，我本來特別著急然後……
Listen, I was in a hurry and...
他們永遠不會相信你的 閃電俠
They'll never believe you, Flash.
這將是我們倆的小秘密
This will be our little secret.
- 那個人是誰啊？- 回來！
- Who's that?- Get back here!
閃電俠 等等
Flash, wait.
還是不夠快
Still not fast enough.
下一次再努力一點
Try harder next time.
受不了了！這次一定得是最後一次
That's it!This is the last time.
閃電俠 等等
Flash, wait.
蝙蝠俠
Batman.
你是不是最強夥伴呀？
Aren't you the best sidekick ever?
沒錯你就是
Yes, you are. Yes, you are.
我也想要蝙蝠俠給我揉揉肚子
Aw, I want a Bat belly rub.
蝙蝠俠 我只是……別擔心
Batman, I just...Don't worry.
我搞定了冷凍隊長 迴旋鏢隊長和小丑
I took care of Captain Cold,Captain Boomerang and the Joker.
謝謝你了？
Thank you?
在一切重新開始之前我只剩幾分鐘了
And I only have a few minutes before it starts all over again.
在什麼重新開始之前？
Before what starts all over again?
關於即將發生的所有事件？一個令人焦慮的情緒狀態？
Referencing events yet to happen?An agitated emotional state?
時間循環
Time loop.
- 沒錯 就是它 - 不可能啊
- Yes, that's it.- Impossible.
這不是我們第一次處理和時間有關的問題了
This isn't our first tangle with time.
在超級英雄界發生過好多回了
Happens a lot in the superhero business.
我一直在不停地過同一天 一遍又一遍
I keep living the same day over and over again.
我感覺我簡直是走到死胡同裡來了
I feel like I've hit a dead end.
一個有趣的事實
Fun fact.
在亞原子層面上，死胡同絕對不是真的死胡同
At the subatomic level, dead ends aren't really dead ends at all.
在分子之間總是存在空隙
There is always space between the molecules
可以容納原子通過而且……
that allow atoms to move between them and...
而且你根本不想聽這些
And you don't care.
所以 蝙蝠俠 我應該怎麼辦？
So, Batman, what should I do?
嗯 要打破時間循環在理論上是可能的
Hmm, it's theoretically possible to break out of a time loop.
但是坦白說 我覺得你還不夠快
But frankly, I don't think you're fast enough.
不夠快？
Not fast enough?
我還以為你知道應該怎麼辦呢 蝙蝠俠
I thought you would have the answer, Batman.
而我錯了
I was wrong.
好強的逆反心理啊 蝙蝠俠
Nice reverse psychology, Batman.
你說的那些正好都是他想聽的
That's just what he needed to hear.
現在他是去什麼地方了？
Now where's he going?
不是什麼地方，而是什麼時間
Not where. When.
看來你還是抓不到我
You still can't seem to catch me.
為什麼它飛不起來呢？
Why won't it fly, Dad?
有風才行
There needs to be a wind.
- 哇！- 兒子！
- Whoa!
- Son!
這太棒啦！
This is amazing!
只需要再快一點點，閃電俠
Just a little faster, Flash.
不要今天不要再來一遍不要……
Not today or again or...
不管怎麼樣了！
Whatever!
一切都完全按照計劃
Everything is going perfectly to plan.
哇啊
Whoa.
嗯 好歹這次沒又回到床上去
Well, at least I'm not in bed again.
但是我現在在哪啊？
But where am I?
我們討厭你 閃電俠
We hate you, Flash.
你這人糟透了 爛透了
You're horrible. You're awful.
真是個大寫的失望
What a phenomenal disappointment.
這是什麼情況？
What was that about?
人人都愛閃電俠呀
Everyone loves the Flash.
至少以前都愛
At least they used to.
好吧 這太瘋狂了 我得回聯盟去
Okay, this is crazy, I need to get back to the League.
奇怪了
That's weird.
再試一次
Let's try that again.
我的速度
My powers.
沒了
They're gone.
我得回正義大廳去
I've gotta get to the Hall!
我的天
Oh, man.
我總算明白為啥大家都不愛跑步了
I can see
why people hate to run.
說不定鋼骨能幫我……
Maybe Cyborg can fix my...
呃 嗨 諸位，幹嘛臉色這麼難看啊？
Uh, hey, guys,why the mean faces?
你給我的披風上了漿
You starched my cape.
你把我的洗發水換成了滅火劑！
You switched my shampoo with fire extinguishing cream!
你亂畫我的隱形飛機
You painted my invisible jet.
現在它……
Now it's just...
它顯形了！
Just visible!
你把我的一隻胳膊換成了打蛋器
You replaced my arm with an egg beater.
雖然這打蛋器很好用啦 但是！
Sure the eggs are amazing,but still.
而且你覺得那樣挺好玩的
And you decided it would be fun
就把我的多功能腰帶上的小袋子全弄混了
to mix up the pouches on my utility belt.
什麼？
What?
不不不 那些都不是我幹的
No, no, I didn't do any of those things,
你們不明白
you don't understand.
之前有一個模模糊糊的傢伙 然後我們開始賽跑然後……
There was this blurry guy and we started running and...
我們不想聽 閃電俠
We don't wanna hear it, Flash.
你至少在正義聯盟搞了52次惡作劇了
You've pulled at least 52 pranks on the Justice League
自從我加入的這五天以來
in the five days since I've joined.
五天？
Five days?
你不是今天早上才加入的嗎？
You just joined this morning.
我在這呆不下去了
I'm outta here.
原子俠是對的
Atom's right.
閃電俠 你的惡作劇應該受到懲罰
Flash, your pranks require punishment.
你被開除了
You're fired.
沒有超能力 沒有聯盟
No power, no League.
我現在該怎麼辦？
What do I do now?
我希望你繼續碌碌無為下去
Fade into obscurity I hope.
嘿 那是我的服裝
Hey, that's my costume.
是嗎？我倒還沒注意
Is it? I hadn't noticed.
是你！
You!
那些惡作劇 時間循環
The pranks, the time loop.
都是你幹的好事
It was all you.
你招惹錯人了
You messed
with the wrong hero,
又黃又模糊的傢伙
yellow blur guy.
時間循環的事你可不能怪在我頭上 巴裡
Uh-uh-uh. Don't blame me for the time loop, Barry.
你自己才是那個非要證明自己是世界上速度最快的人的那個傻瓜
You were the fool that had to prove you were the fastest man alive.
但是你不知道什麼是神速力吧 對不？
But you didn't know about the Speed Force, did you?
這種力量可以穿越所有的時間和空間
A force that runs through all of space and time.
每次你追我追到神速力賽道的時候
Every time you chased me into the Speedway,
我就一次又一次地把你帶回同一天重複地過
I led you backwards in time to relive the same day over and over.
趁你困在你的時間循環裡的時候
And while you were stuck in your time loop,
我讓所有人都與你為敵
I turned everyone against you,
然後我騙你切斷了自己的神速力
and then tricked you into severing your Speed Force power.
但是為什麼？我哪裡得罪你了？
But why? What did I ever do to you?
你哪裡得罪……？
What did you...
你哪樣沒得罪我？
What didn't you do?
閃電俠 未來的史書上說
The Flash, according to future history books,
你是整個世界最愛的超級英雄
the world's favorite hero.
又幽默 又完美
So funny, so perfect.
速度還那麼快！
So fast!
但是我更快
But I'm faster.
可惜 我一直生活在你的陰影下的話 沒人會認識到我的偉大
Yet, nobody will recognize my greatness while I live in your shadow.
這就是為什麼我
That is why I,
逆閃電
the Reverse-Flash,
要穿越回到過去毀了你
have traveled back in time to ruin you.
所以 你來自未來
So, you're from the future
你還管自己叫逆閃電？
and you call yourself Reverse-Flash?
呃 真的嗎？我是說……
Ugh. Really? I mean...
- 你是倒著跑還是怎麼樣？- 不是
- Do you run backwards or something?- No.
- 那你是超級慢嗎？- 才不是
- Are you super slow?- No.
我只是一切都跟你相反
I'm just the reverse of you.
你是好人我是壞人
You're good and I'm bad.
那你為什麼不叫邪惡閃電？
Then wouldn't you be called Evil Flash
或者壞閃電？
or Bad Flash?
我就是逆閃 好嗎？
I'm just Reverse-Flash, okay?
隨你啦
Okay.
夠了
That's enough of that.
拜託了 巴裡 你知道是什麼回事
Please, Barry.You know how it is.
我 快
Me, fast,
你 慢
you, slow.
現在你已經被我擊敗了
Now that you've been beaten,
是時候讓世界都知道
it's time for the world to know
誰才是一直以來最偉大的極速者
who is truly the greatest speedster of all time.
我在正義聯盟的朋友會阻止你的
My friends in the Justice League will stop you.
你的朋友？
Your friends?
是指那些剛把你踢出門外的人嗎？
You mean the people that just kicked you out of their club?
我跟你說吧 巴裡
Well, I'll tell you what, Barry.
既然你這麼在乎他們
Since you care for them so much
那我下一步就去”照顧“他們
I'm going to take care of them next.
看起來閃電俠說的都是真話
Looks like Flash was telling the truth.
這個逆閃電角色把他困在時間循環裡
This Reverse-Flash character kept him in a time loop
趁機毀了他的名聲
while he ruined his reputation.
這個混蛋
That rotten rascal.
- 我把手銬打破了- 別擔心 閃電俠
- I broke 'em.- Don't worry, Flash.
等我變大以後，我們就一起把一切都告訴正義聯盟
Once I enlarge, we'll inform the Justice League together
然後阻止這個速度很快的傢伙 嗯？
and stop this
fast-paced villain. Hmm?
呃 這可壞了
Oh, this isn't good. This isn't good at all.
我的縮身腰帶肯定是剛才手銬放電的時候燒短路了
My white dwarf shrinking belt must've shorted out when those shackles stunned Flash,
連通訊系統也燒壞了
along with my communication systems.
閃電俠！你能聽見我說話嗎？
Flash! Can you hear me?
- 閃電俠！閃電俠 這裡啊 閃電俠 - 這下好了
- Flash! Flash, over here, Flash.- Great.
我現在該怎麼辦？超能力沒了
What do I do now?I'm powerless.
我的朋友們 要是還能稱作朋友的話 已經把我踢出聯盟了
My friends, if you can call them that, kicked me out of the League.
唉 這種事怎麼會發生在我身上啊
Oh, this can't be happening to me.
你覺得你那算事兒？
You think you have problems?
我太小了 人家看不到也聽不到我
I'm too small to be seen or heard.
至少你還能拿起電話找人聊聊……
At least you can pick up the phone and talk to some...
等等
Wait a second.
我不能幫閃電俠找回超能力
I can't give Flash his powers back.
但是我知道有人也許做得到
But I know someone who might.
擋在我和幫助閃電俠中間的唯一障礙
And the only thing that stands between me and helping the Flash...
不過就是水果沙拉嘛
Is fruit salad.
這能有多難呢？
How hard can this be?
好的！
Yes!
哈！
Ha!
嗯？哦
Huh? Oh.
真是怪了 一般我不小心用屁股撥了號的話
That's weird,usually when I butt-dial,
我的屁股通常在手機附近啊
my butt is actually near the phone.
歡迎來到命運博士的魔力幫助熱線
Welcome to Doctor Fate's magic helpline.
你覺得整個世界都與你為敵嗎？
Do you feel like the world's turned against you?
是啊是啊 我覺得
Yes, yes, I do.
你覺得自己的腳步失去了活力嗎？
Do you feel like you've lost that pep in your step?
哦 哇哦 是啊 我失去了所有的活力呢
Oh, wow. Yeah,I've lost all my pep.
你覺得有人想要取代你生活中的位置嗎？
Do you feel like someone is trying to take your place in life?
也許是把你踢出一個俱樂部或聯盟？
Maybe kick you out of a club?Or League?
我不認識這傢伙 但是他確實有兩下子啊
I don't know who this guy is,but he is good.
嗯 如果上面那些情況有任何一條發生在你身上
Well, if any of that applies to you,
結結實實幫自己一把吧 請按1 就現在
do yourself a solid and press one, now.
嗯 巴裡 希望這個能有幫助吧
Well, Barry,let's hope this helps.
什麼？
Huh?
等等 等等 等等！
Wait, wait, wait!
我要跟你一起去
I'm going with you.
看來我不得不採取艱難方法了
It looks like I'm going to have to do this the hard way.
我必須得趕到大都會去
I'll just have to get to Metropolis
通知正義聯盟到底發生了什麼事
and tell the Justice League everything that's happened.
應該也沒有多難嘛
It shouldn't be that hard.
我只要從閃電俠的門縫底下溜出去 跳上一輛公交車 然後……
I'll just slip under Flash's front door, hop on a bus and...
哦 不是吧
Oh, no.
現在閃電俠走了
Now that the Flash is gone,
我們得另外找人來做會議紀錄
we'll need someone else to take the minutes.
哦 我 我 我！
Oh! Me! Me! Me!
- 鋼骨 - 耶
- Cyborg?- Yes.
看起來麻煩事在整個地圖上不斷出現啊
It looks like trouble is springing up all over the map.
好吧 隊友們 我們分頭行事 搞定它們
All right, team, split up and let's take care of business.
鋼骨 把剛才那些念一遍給我聽
Cyborg, read that back to me.
好吧 隊員們 我們分頭行事 搞定它們
"All right, team, split up and let's take care of business.
鋼骨 把剛才那些念一遍給我聽
"Cyborg, read that back to me."
很好 我們行動吧
Good job, let's move.
“做-的-好”
"Good job.
我們-行-動-吧
"Let's M-O-V-E."
人類已經在蔬菜沙拉自助餐台旁邊狼吞虎咽太久了
Too long have humans gorged themselves at the salad bar.
現在是時候讓蔬菜植物們在人類自助餐台旁邊飽餐一頓了
Now it's time for the plants to gorge at the human bar.
住手
Stop.
我是市長 我命令你住手
I'm the Mayor,I command you to stop.
不好意思啦 毒藤女
Sorry, Poison Ivy.
我聽到有人在尖叫
I heard someone screaming.
你懂的嘛 “我尖叫，你尖叫”
And you know,"I scream, you scream,
“大家一起把冰淇淋叫”
"we all scream for ice cream."
拿下他
Get him.
哦 天吶
Oh, man.
蔬菜植物應該是用來看的 不是用來聽的
- Plants should be seen, not heard.
“市長的溫布利花園”
"Wimbley for Mayor"?
一個市長花車 哦！
A mayoral float! Oh!
- 謝謝你啊，這位……- 我的名字是逆閃電
- Thank you, Mr...- Reverse-Flash is my name
幫助他人是我的工作
and helping people out is my game.
現在 我必須要走了
Now, I must be away.
還有很多其他需要我幫助的市民們在等著我
There are other citizens that need my help.
信號手錶 信號手錶
Signal watch. Signal watch.
快來啊 超人
Come on, Superman.
這回可要給奧爾森你好好上一課 不準找壞角度拍我醜照
This will teach Olsen not to take a photo of my bad side.
我很抱歉 鱷魚先生
I'm sorry, Mr. Croc.
只不過 拍你的話哪一面都是壞角度啊
It's just, with you every side is a bad side.
殺手鱷！
Killer Croc!
放開超人的朋友 吉米·奧爾森
Unhand Superman's pal,Jimmy Olsen.
絕不！
Never!
我能搞定 塑膠
I've got this, Plas.
我也能切開木頭 超人 快看
I can cut logs, too, Supes,check it out.
塑膠！
Plas!
啊 哦
Uh-oh.
你是怎麼做到的？
How did you do that?
對逆閃來說只是小孩子的把戲罷了
Child's play for Reverse-Flash.
這麼說 你應該沒有信號手錶吧 對嗎？
Say, I don't suppose you have a signal watch, do you?
喪鐘！
Deathstroke!
他正在偷我們船上裝黃金的貨櫃！
He's stealing our shipment of gold!
黃金是你在未來的一項非常好的投資
Gold is a great investment in your future.
但是你唯一的未來將在監獄裡過了
But the only future you've got is behind bars.
只用一天就能搞定的 只有我……
All in a day's work for...
逆閃電
Reverse-Flash.
逆閃電最棒了！
Reverse-Flash is the best!
逆閃電 你做到了！
Reverse-Flash, you did it.
在海上遇到麻煩了嗎？
Trouble at sea?
海王已上線
Aquaman is in.
逆閃電已經搞定了
Reverse-Flash took care of it.
海王已下線
Aquaman is out.
感覺好尷尬
I'm embarrassed.
但是又有點被驚到了
But I'm also a little impressed.
好了 企鵝人 放下你的武器
All right, Penguin,drop your weapon.
是的 我會放下武器的 好吧
Yeah. I'll drop my weapon,all right.
朝你放！
On you!
先等我把你放倒再說
Not before I get the drop on you.
蝙蝠俠剛剛把導彈發射了
Batman just launched the missile.
我們死定了！
We're doomed!
別擔心 逆閃電會搞定
Don't worry. Reverse-Flash will take care of it.
什麼？
What?
萬歲！
Hurray!
他蓋了一個安全到完美的遊樂場
He built a perfectly safe playground
- 用的是會爆炸導彈的零件 -真厲害
- out of explosive missile parts.- Amazing.
一片好意來自於……
Courtesy of the...
逆閃電
Reverse-Flash.
耶 讓我們聽聽給逆閃電的掌聲和歡呼吧
Yeah. Let's hear it for Reverse-Flash.
逆閃電？
Reverse-Flash, huh?
唔
Hmm.
那可怪了
That was weird.
不過也沒有飄浮的城堡那麼怪
But not like floating castle weird.
哇哦 魔力樓梯
Wow. Magical stairs.
如果是魔力自動扶梯就更好了
I wish there was a magic escalator.
嗯？
Huh?
是啊 呃……
Yeah, um...
我在倒著說話
I'm talking backwards.
進來就行了 好嗎？
Just come in, okay?
哦 好的
Okay, sure.
你們還真的很喜歡爬樓梯呢
Wow. You guys really like stairs.
閃電俠 請上前來
Flash, come forward.
博士和你的命運在等著你
The Doctor is in and your fate awaits.
- 謝謝 - 不客氣
- Thanks.- You're welcome.
扎塔娜[扎塔娜：DC超級英雄 100位最性感女性漫畫人物表中名列第四]
Zatanna.
真不敢相信說倒話101是一個魔力規定
I can't believe backwards talking 101 is a magic requirement.
- 扎塔娜 - 對不起！哦 我是說 起不對！
- Zatanna!- Sorry! Uh, I mean, "Yrros."
是的 那樣一點都不奇怪
Yeah, that's
not strange at all.
哇啊！
Huh? Whoa!
這是我人生中進入過的第二詭異的房間了
This is the second weirdest room I've ever been in.
不要怕 走近點
- Don't be afraid. Come closer.- Huh?
歡迎來到我的神秘聖殿
Welcome to my sanctum.
- 我是……- 閃電俠 我知道
- I'm the...- Flash, I know.
我是命運博士
I'm Doctor Fate.
很高興終於見到你了
It's nice to finally meet you.
請說出你的憂鬱之藍吧 然後我們 呃 解決它
Please tell me your blues, and we'll, uh, sort it out.
我的憂鬱之藍？
My blues?
嗯 幾天前 我被困在一個時間循環裡了
Well, a couple of days ago,I was stuck in a time loop.
好吧 呃 她會一直這樣做嗎？
Okay, uh,does she always do that?
這是魔力 夥計！你繼續說
It's magic, man! Keep going.
呃 好的
Um, okay.
我一直不停地重複那一天
? I kept repeating the day
在一個什麼宇宙高速上追著個反派跑
? And chasing a villain on some cosmic freeway
但是他總是跑得比我快
? But he was always faster than me
然後我的超能力就沒了
? And then my powers went away
啊 唱出來吧 哥們兒
Ah, sing it, man.
當我回到家每個人都在生我的氣
? I came back home and everyone was mad
讓我卷起包袱走人
? Told me to leave and handed me my bag
實際上吧 是個盒子
Actually, it was a box.
- 但是……- 不要現在停下來嘛
- But...- Don't stop now.
所以我坐在沙發上 思考要怎麼辦
? So as I sat on my couch wonderin' what to do
我的手機響起來 那頭就是你
? My phone started ringing and it was you
你聽到這個電話不用慌
? You heard the callNo need to panic
因為這是來點魔力的時候了
? 'Cause it's time for a little magic
這是魔力 寶貝
? It's magic, baby
除了魔力沒別的
? That's all that it is
魔力 寶貝 只是一點小魔力
? Magic, baby It's just a little magic
要想弄懂它 寶貝 你無需天賦異稟
? To understand it, baby,you don't have to be a whiz
聽吧
Listen.
當生活把你放倒 當你無處可去
? When life's got you down with nowhere to go
只要卷起袖子奏響樂章
r? Just roll up you sleeves and presto
當你把手伸進帽子裡 把煩惱統統拉出來
? When you reach in your hat and pull out a problem
你需要的答案 魔法可以給你
? You need some answers and magic's got 'em
因為它是魔力 寶貝
? 'Cause it's magic, baby
是時候把它拿下了
? Time to get it done
魔力 寶貝 只是一點小小的魔力
? Magic, baby It's just a little magic
這是魔力 寶貝
? It's magic, baby
現在讓我們來樂一樂吧
? So now let's have some fun ?
哇哦 那真是……
Wow! That was...
魔力哇
Magic.
不管怎麼說吧 你的魔力能告訴我為啥我失去超能力了呢？
Anyway, can your magic tell me why I've lost my powers?
唔
Hmm.
看起來你和神速力的連接斷了
It looks like your connection to the Speed Force is broken.
神速力？
Speed Force?
逆閃也說過關於它的事
Reverse-Flash said something about that.
但是我完全不懂他在說什麼
But I have no idea what he meant.
什麼是神速力？
What's the Speed Force?
一種神秘的能量
A mysterious energy
那種能量能帶來超高速運動的能力
that grants the ability to move at super speed.
哦 是我獲得能力的那天嗎？
Oh. The day I got my powers?
那完全是意外啊
That was a total fluke.
你看 當時有些閃電然後這些化學藥劑潑在我身上了……
You see, there was this lightning and then these chemicals spilled on me...
那是你以為的
That's what you thought.
真相是你是被選中成為閃電俠的
The reality is that you were chosen to be the Flash.
這些超能力是賜予你的一項天賦
These powers are a gift given to you
來自於神速力
from the Speed Force.
但是你們之間的聯繫斷掉了
But your connection to it was broken.
所以 現在咋辦 你能修復嗎？
So, what now? Can you fix it?
並不能
No.
但我能把你帶到神速力所在之處
But I can take you to where the Speed Force lives.
- 它的所在之處？- 是的
- Where it lives?- Yes.
我們將要去往
We're going to
神速力之地
the Speed Force Zone.
神速力之地 聽起來好厲害啊
The Speed Force Zone. That sounds awesome.
退後
Step back.
現在是魔力時間
It's magic time.
命運的力量和統一的智慧啊
With the force of fate and wits unified,
用一段絕妙的旅程送我們一程吧
take us away on a groovy ride.
- 野外考察！- 扎塔娜
- Whoo-hoo! Field trip!
- Zatanna?
起不對
Yrros.
那是我追逆閃電的時候跑過的地方
That's... That's the place I saw when I
was running after the Reverse-Flash.
它叫神速力賽道
It's called the Speedway.
神速之地的門戶
Our gateway to the Speed Force Zone.
日誌輸入編號13
Journal entry 13.
事情發展一點也不按計劃走
Things have not gone as planned.
無法回到我的正常大小
Unable to grow to my normal size,
我周遭的世界已經變得比你能想象到的要危險得多
the world around me has become more dangerous than you can possibly imagine.
每一輛車，都是一場山崩地裂的大災難
Every car, a cataclysm.
每一隻老鼠 都是一頭狂野巨獸
Every mouse, a monster.
每一米路程 都是一場馬拉松
Every meter, a marathon.
所有實驗都始於一個問題，那麼我的問題來了
Experiments always start with a question.Here's mine.
我要怎麼才能活著回去啊？
How am I going to survive?
這是今天發回來的畫面
That was the scene today,
畫面內容是逆閃電持續進行著他的一系列史無前例的英雄行為，
as the Reverse-Flash continues his unprecedented streak of heroism.
看起來逆閃電是獨一無二的超級英雄
It would seem that the Reverse-Flash is the only superhero
這個世界有他就足夠了
the world will ever need.
看看那個麻煩事兒警報地圖
Just look at that trouble alert map.
逆閃電太快了 他在阻止的犯罪是我們甚至還沒……
Reverse-Flash is so fast, he's stopping crime before we can even...
終於有個緊急情況了
Finally an emergency.
嗷，唉
Aw, yeah!
又被他搶先了
He got there first.
他今天一天就搞定了22樁緊急事件
That's 22 emergencies he's fixed today.
而且他剛剛在超級英雄臉書上排名超過我了
And he's just passed me in friends on Herobook.
嗯  像這樣的事根本不重要 也算好事一樁
Well, it's a good thing things like this aren't important at all
對我這樣的鋼鐵之軀來說
to the Man of Steel.
看起來逆閃似乎
It seems that the Reverse-Flash
已經同意與市長坐下來進行一場對話
has agreed to sit down for a chat with the Mayor.
不要轉檯 我們即將現場直播
Stay tuned for live coverage
我們心愛的超級英雄極速者
of our beloved heroic speedster.
我覺得現在是時候跟這位談談了
I think it's about time we had a word with this
這位心愛的極速者
beloved speedster.
我要拿回我的超能力了 我要拿回我的超能力了！
Whoo-hoo! I'm gonna get my powers back!I'm gonna get my powers back!
但是首先 我得來點零食墊墊肚子
But, uh, first,I might need a snack.
謝謝
Thank you.
你不是應該在開車嗎？
Shouldn't you be driving?
別擔心
Don't worry.
博士剛剛給我魔法師的免手動駕駛許可
The Doc just gave me my magician's permit for hands-free driving.
- 扎塔娜 - 起不對
- Zatanna. - Yrros.
現在你聽好了 當你到達神速之地的時候
Now listen, when you arrive at the Speed Force Zone,
你將會經受一系列的考驗
you'll go through a series of tests
來證明你有這個資格
to make sure you're worthy.
有啥資格？
Worthy of what?
那就是你要弄明白的事
That's what you need to find out.
那就是秘密
That's the mystery.
那就是魔力
That's the magic.
是 好吧 但是你會留在那幫我的 對吧？
Yeah. Yeah. But you'll be there to help me, right?
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
神速之地只允許
The Speed Force Zone is only accessible
擁有神速力的人接近
to those with speed powers.
或者是你這種情況 擁有過神速力的人
Or in your case,former speed powers.
嗯 就是這樣了
Well, this is it.
- 有什麼臨別贈言嗎？ - 有噠
- Any parting words?- Yeah.
亡羊補牢 寶貝兒
Tuck and roll, baby.
亡羊補牢？
Tuck and roll?
- 那是什麼意……？- 起不對啦
- What is that...- Yrros.
啊
Oh.
哇啊
Whoa.
哇哦，你看到沒
Wow. Would you look at that?
它是某種神速之地的神廟之類的玩意兒
It's some sort of Speed Force Zone temple thingy.
而且感覺那個神廟正在散髮出某種能量
And it almost feels like the temple is giving off some sort of energy.
神速力！
The Speed Force!
如果那就是神速力所在之處
If that's where the Speed Force is,
那就是我要去的地方了，要快
that's where I need to be,and fast.
好吧，這些肯定就是命運博士說的那些考驗了
All right. These must be the tests Doctor Fate was talking about.
磚頭移動速度超級快，還能振動穿過堅硬的固體
Bricks moving superfast, vibrating through solid matter.
而我需要做的只是成功跑到那一頭去
And I just have to make it to the other side.
嗯 這應該不是很難的
Well, this shouldn't be too hard.
那些磚塊衝擊力好強啊
Those speed bricks really pack a wallop,
但是如果你起初沒有成功……
but if at first you don't succeed...
好吧 這招不好使
Okay.
This is not working.
肯定有個竅門的
There has to be a trick.
我們希望你能成為你可以成為的最好的超級英雄……
We want you to be the best hero you can be.
有時候那意味要放慢速度
Sometimes that means slowing down.
嗯 慢下來
Mmm. Slow down.
歐耶 謝啦 超人
Yeah, thanks, Supe.
嗯 快跑行不通 而且命運博士說我會被考驗
Well, going fast didn't work,and Fate said I'd be tested.
這怎麼起效的？
How is this working?
我真的 真的 真的討厭慢慢走
I really, really, really hate going slow.
天吶
Holy moly.
還真管用了！我做到了！
It actually worked!I did it!
小菜一碟嘛
Piece of cake.
日誌輸入編號14
Journal entry 14.
情況變得粘乎乎毫無進展
The situation has grown sticky.
但我必須保留我身上的智慧
But I must keep my wits about me.
我必須要動用身邊的一切可用之物來保命
I must use everything at my disposal to survive.
我必須用到，科學！
I must use science!
關於蛛形綱的一個小小的廣為人知的假說
A little known hypothesis about arachnids
就是他們會被閃爍的光源催眠
is that they can be hypnotized by flashing lights.
是時候驗證一下這個理論了
Time to test that theory.
科學會贏嗎？
Can science prevail?
還是蜘蛛會取勝呢？
Will the spider be hypnotized?
難道我將在蜘蛛體內學習它的消化過程嗎？
Will I learn about spider digestion from the inside?
有了！
Eureka!
啊哈！
Aha!
研究表明部分鳥類會被馴化
Studies have shown tha some birds can be tamed
通過在後背上的某處特殊神經施加一點點壓力
by applying gentle pressure to a special nerve on the back.
這隻家鴿證明了那些研究的正確性
This Columba livia domestica proves those studies correct.
那麼現在就去正義大廳吧
And now to the Hall of Justice.
希望我來得及通知正義聯盟
Hopefully, I'm in time to alert the League
趕在逆閃造成更多破壞之前
before Reverse-Flash can do any more damage.
哦 我懂了
Oh, I get it.
我手機上有這個小遊戲
I have this game on my phone.
我只要想辦法跳上這些板塊一直跳到頂就可以了
All I have to do is ride these to the top.
哇啊 好痛
Ow! Whoa. That hurt.
說不定這個是某種耐力考驗
Maybe this is some sort of endurance test.
我必須要表現出我能扛得住
I just have to show I can take it.
我扛不住啊啊啊！
I can't take it!
留意你的周圍
Be aware of your surroundings.
我的周圍？
My surroundings?
我之前從沒注意過那些平台
I never noticed those platforms before.
哇哦 通向大門的路一直就在那裡啊
Wow, the path to the door was there the whole time.
哈！小菜一碟 檸檬……
Ha! Easy-peasy, lemon...
還是好痛 還是好痛
Still hurts. Still hurts.
感謝你加入我們 逆閃電
Thank you for joining us,Reverse-Flash.
這是我的榮幸 市長
It's my pleasure, Mayor.
能為社群服務 我十分榮幸
I serve with the pleasure of the community.
你不會在什麼私人小島上的俱樂部別墅裡看到我，不會的
You won't see me in some private island clubhouse, no.
我就愛當人民公僕啊
I love being the servant of the people.
你真令人敬佩
You're incredible.
你不僅阻止了毒藤女和她那些發狂的植物
Not only did you stop Poison Ivy and her maniacal plants, you...
我們為什麼要在這鬼鬼崇崇的？
Why are we sneaking around?
你要懂得這就是蝙蝠俠做事的風格
You know this is how Batman does things.
我們正在暗中監視逆閃
We're spying on Reverse-Flash,
因為蝙蝠俠覺得自己最終會給他使個絆子
because Batman thinks he'll eventually trip up
把他真實的邪惡目的暴露人前
and reveal his true evil intentions.
正確 鋼骨
Correct, Cyborg.
這是一次秘密偵查
This is a covert op.
我們將會從暗影處窺探 在暗影中行動
We'll spy from the shadows,move in the shadows,
成為……
be the...
火風暴 把你腦袋燈關了
Firestorm,turn down your head.
哦 抱歉
Oh. Sorry.
我的謙遜質樸不允許我取得任何的褒獎 市長小姐
Modesty forbids me from taking such praise, Miss Mayor.
說起哥譚市
And speaking of Gotham City,
你知道蝙蝠俠和羅賓被巨石砸中叫什麼嗎？
為啥，不知道啊
- do you know what you call Batman and Robin under a rock?- Why, no.
扁平男和羅帶賓
Flatman and Ribbon.
哦哦 還有個段子 請問鋼骨什麼時候換褲子？
Oh! Here's another. When does Cyborg change his pants?
永遠不換 他根本沒穿褲子
Never. He's not wearing any.
噓……
Shh.
我肯定每一位在家看電視的觀眾都會同意
As I'm sure everyone at home would agree,
你已經讓大都會和整個世界都變得更加安全
you have made Metropolis and the world a safer place.
你作為一個超級英雄 既不要求榮譽授勛
You're a hero that never asks for accolades
也不會穿那種很浮誇的披風之類的東西
or wears something as gaudy as a cape.
浮誇？浮誇？
- Gaudy?
因為這些
And for that,
我們想要授予你一項榮譽
we'd like to honor you
城市之匙
with the key to the city.
感謝大家 大都會善良的居民們
Thank you,
fine citizens of Metropolis.
我接受你們一文不值的……我是說珍貴的 禮物
I accept your paltry...I mean, precious gift.
很快這個世界就將意識到 其實你們已經明白了
Soon the world will realize what you have already learned.
我 逆閃電
That I, Reverse-Flash,
是你們唯一需要的超級英雄
am the only hero you will ever need.
不要啊 塑膠人
No, Plastic Man.
你在支撐橫梁上放太多重量了
You're putting too much weight on the support beam.
你得……
You need to...
這就是為什麼蝙蝠俠單獨行動
This is why the Batman works alone.
哦 看吶！
Oh, look!
是正義聯盟
It's the Justice League.
或者我應該叫你們失業者聯盟？
Or should I say the Jobless League.
悲催的是 我同意
Sadly, I agree.
這隻能說明一件事
- Huh?- This can only mean one thing.
正義聯盟現在宣布退休
The Justice League is now retired.
迷宮？我最喜歡迷宮了
A maze?Well, I love mazes!
它們可棒了
They're amazing.
我快到了 我能感覺到我的力量正回來呢
I'm almost there. I can feel my powers coming back.
嗨 幾乎回覆到全速了
Hey, look at that.
Almost back to full speed.
耶！哦 不是吧
Yeah! Oh, no. Huh?
所以我要做的就是在一片漆黑中穿過這個迷宮嗎？
So all I have to do is get through the maze in the dark.
有我的超能力 那應該不是什麼問題
With my super speed back,that shouldn't be a problem.
好吧 那確實是個問題
Okay. It's a problem!
這個地方有什麼東西一直想傷害我呢？
What is it with this place trying to hurt me?
蝙蝠俠說什麼來著？
What was it Batman said?
總是準備一套計劃 總是準備一套計劃
- Always have a plan.- Always have a plan.
好的 那麼 閃電 你的計劃是什麼？
Okay, so, Flash,what's your plan?
哦！我可以從高處這裡提前做好計劃
Oh! I can make a plan from up here.
好了 現在我們看看
Okay. Now let's see.
左 右 右 右 等下 不 不不不不
Left, right, right, right.Wait, no, no, no, no.
左 右 右 右 左
Okay. Left, right, right,
right, left...
左 右 左
Okay. Left, right, left,
左 右 左 右 左 左
left, right, left, right,left, left,
右 右 左 左 左 完美
right, right, left, left.Perfect.
好了 我搞定了 我搞定了
Okay, I got it. I got it.
最後一道門了
The final door.
啊 拜託 我怎麼才能通過這扇堅固的大門？
Aw, come on! How can I get through this solid door?
這是個死胡同嘛！
It's a dead end!
有趣的事實
Fun fact.
在亞原子層面上
At the subatomic level,
死胡同絕對不是真的死胡同
dead ends aren't really dead ends at all.
分子之間總會存在空隙
There is always space between the molecules
允許原子子從中間通過
that allow atoms to move between them.
如果原子俠是對的
If the Atom is right,
一切事物之間都有空隙的話
and there is space between everything,
我需要做的就是像神速磚那樣，
I just have to do what the speed bricks did
把自己振動成分子狀態從事物的空隙中穿過去
and vibrate my molecules to fit between them.
嗯 來吧 一切就靠這個了
Well, here goes everything.
我剛剛振動通過那堵暀F
I just vibrated through that wall.
我無所不能啊！
I can do anything!
就是這裡了
That's it.
我能感覺到它在激發出神速力
I can feel it radiating the Speed Force.
哇哦！
Wow!
它是某種核心
It's some kind of nexus.
太驚人了！
It's amazing!
我終於做到了！
I've finally done it!
沒有什麼能阻止我……
Nothing can stop...
終於！
At last!
逆閃？
Reverse-Flash?
- 但是怎麼會這樣？ - 還是慢半拍，對不？
- But how?- Still too slow, aren't you?
時間循環
The time loop.
你打破了你與神速力之間的連接
You breaking your connection to the Speed Force,
我早知道它會引導你來到這裡
I knew it would all lead you here,
來到神速力之核
to the Speed Force nexus.
而且 通過那個荒謬的障礙機關
And also, through that ridiculous obstacle course...
我說 你是不是在逗我？
I mean, are you kidding me?
多危險啊！
Dangerous!
所以我忽悠你為我打開這三道門
So I duped you into opening
the three doors for me.
恭喜你啦 失敗者！
Congratulations, loser!
現在嘛
And now,
取得了神速力之核的力量
with the power of the nexus,
再沒有什麼東西能阻擋我了
nothing can stand in my way.
這力量
The power!
感覺 感覺像是連喝了52杯奶昔
It's... It's like drinking 52 milkshakes
又吃下整整一大袋果凍軟糖！
and eating a bag of jelly beans!
精神百倍！
Invigorating!
神速力之核是我的！我努力贏來的！
The nexus is mine!I earned it!
祝你們好運吧，你們將被永遠困在這裡
Good luck being trapped here for all eternity.
我真沒法相信我們要退休了
I can't believe that we're retiring.
我是說 我們將何去何從啊？
I mean,where do we go from here?
英雄們 鋼骨 永遠不要放棄希望
Heroes, Cyborg,never give up hope.
而我 還沒有放棄調查逆閃
And I haven't given up investigating Reverse-Flash.
哦 巨星隕落啊
Oh, how the mighty have fallen.
一度輝煌的正義聯盟
The once great Justice League
被迫退休
forced into retirement.
面對現實吧 超級狗熊們
Face it, super zeroes,
你們已經是昨日黃花了
you're yesterday's news!
快節奏的今日世界需要一個青出於藍的英雄人物
Today's fast-paced world needs a hero like yours truly.
還得謝謝你們的老朋友 閃電俠
And thanks to your old pal, Flash,
未來的史冊上將只會記得我
future history books will know only me
是地球上最偉大的冠軍戰士
as Earth's greatest champion.
瞧著吧
Watch.
快看外面！
Look, outside!
他在幹什麼？
What is he doing?
他在用晲荍x住我們
He's walling us in.
他肯定對我的超級力量一無所知
He must not be aware of my super strength.
對我的嬗變能力也一無所知
Or my ability to transform matter.
我來得太晚了！
I'm too late!
那是什麼材料築成的啊？
What kind of material is that?
肯定不是尋常的種類
Not the normal kind.
我的掃描儀顯示這些磚塊正在以令人難以置信的速度在移動
My scanners indicate these bricks are moving at an incredible speed.
它們放射出的動力學能量
The kinetic energy they're putting off
足以抵消我們所有的超能力
is enough to counteract any of our powers.
你說得太對了，鋼骨
Right you are, Cybore.
這些是來自神速力之地的神速磚
Those are speed bricks from the Speed Force Zone.
只有我一個人覺得那像是瞎編的嗎？
Does that sound made-up to anyone else?
享受你們餘下的幾天吧
Enjoy the rest of your days
困在你們小小的俱樂部別墅裡
trapped inside your little clubhouse.
哦 還有件事
Oh, one more thing.
我已經啟動了你們正義大廳的安全系統
I've activated your Hall of Justice security systems
並且裝備了反攻裝置
and equipped them with countermeasures
專門針對你們的超能力
for each of your powers.
所以你們在裡面可要小心一點喲
So you might wanna be careful in there.
毀滅 毀滅
Destroy. Destroy.{\r
不是吧
Not my cybots!
你這個禽獸
You monster.
我們怎麼辦？
What do we do?
對抗我設計的最強大的安保系統？
Against the most powerful security system I've ever devised?
我們跑
We run.
我怎麼會這麼蠢啊
How could I have bee so stupid?
每一步我都沒逃出逆閃的掌心
At every step, I've played into the Reverse-Flash's hand.
他搶走了我的超能力
He took away my powers.
他搶走了我的朋友
He took away my friends.
哦 我只想回家
Oh, I just wanna go home.
它在振動 就好像……
It's vibrating, like...
就好像神速力在它們裡面一樣
Like they have the Speed Force inside of them.
我有個計劃了
I have a plan.
不錯
Not bad.
相當不錯
Not bad at all.
現在來看下這些神速磚有多厲害
Now let's see what these speed bricks can do.
喔啊！
Whoa!
我所有的努力
All my hard work,
所有的嘗試和磨難
all the trials and tribulations,
一無所得
for nothing.
超級寵物！哈！
The Super-Pets! Huh.
逆閃搞出這麼大亂子
All this trouble with Reverse-Flash
他們居然只是在挖坑！
and they're just digging a hole!
在椪琠酗U挖
Under the wall.
當然了！太機智了！
Of course! Brilliant!
嗨 哥們兒 等等我！
Hey, guys, wait for me!
鋼骨的實驗室
Cyborg's laboratory.
好樣的 兄弟們
Great job, gang.
現在我可以用鋼骨的工具把我的縮身腰帶修好
Now I can use Cyborg's tools to repair my shrinking belt
然後變回正常大小
and return to normal size.
嗨
Hey.
我已經搜集到足夠的信息了
Well, I've collected enough data.
你們倆到底也不是太差勁嘛
You guys aren't so bad after all.
警報！警報！
Alert! Alert!
你們必須被清除
You must be eliminated.
太神奇了
Fascinating.
綠燈俠也有一個寵物
Green Lantern has a pet,
而且還是個晃著圓尾巴的松鼠？
and he's a ring-wielding squirrel?
嗨 你喊誰寵物呢？
Hey! Who you calling pet,short stack?
你會說話啊？
You can talk?
廢話 因為我才不是什麼松鼠
Yeah, because I ain't no squirrel.
我叫大B
Name's B'dg.
我是從另一個星球來的
I'm from another planet
我們星球上的人好死不死恰好長得有點像你們的松鼠
of people that happen to loosely resemble your squirrels.
我明白了 嗯 好有道理
I see. Well, that makes perfect sense.
能獲得您的認可我真是開心
Oh, I'm so glad you approve.
我的好兄弟大A從這裡發出了一個警報
My buddy Ace here sent down an alert.
我來猜猜哈，
Let me guess,
正義聯盟有危險了？
the Justice League is in trouble?
旺旺
Bark.
慣例如此啊
As per usual.
嗯 我們去救他們吧 再一次
Well, let's go rescue them, again.
有沒有誰能解釋一下
Can someone explain
逆閃是怎麼控制我的鋼骨機器人的？
how Reverse-Flash can turn my cybots against us?
他的超級速度不知怎麼的被增強了
Somehow his speed power's been supercharged.
是時候撤退然後想出個計劃來了
Time to fall back and form a plan.
已經被逼到懸崖邊上了 我真希望閃電俠在這裡
By the toenails of Tartarus,I wish that Flash was here.
嗨 各位 在這邊！
Hey, guys, over here!
清除 清除
Eliminate. Eliminate.
多謝及時出手相救啊 夥計們
Thanks forthe quick save, gang.
我不可能在這頂一輩子
I can't hold them off forever.
我們得想辦法找路離開這裡
We need to find a way out of here.
離開這個天堂嗎？
And leave this paradise?
誰會知道海王的臥室
Who knew Aquaman's bedroom
簡直就是星球最佳日間水療浴場呢
was like the best day spa in the planet?
噢，哈！
Ooh, ha!
當然了，海之王就是應該有張水床
Of course, the king of the sea has a waterbed.
- 塑膠！- 各位？
- Plas!- Guys?
挺住啊 超人 超級寵物們有個計劃
Hang in there, Superman.The Super-Pets have a plan.
人家不是寵物
Not a pet.
我相信他們在呼喚什麼人
I believe they're calling someone.
你現在都會說狗語了？
You speak dog now?
不會啊，我只是理解我的朋友們
No, I just understand my friends.
一隻海馬？
A seahorse?
又來一隻超級寵物？
Yet another Super-Pet?
再說一次 人家不是寵物
Again, not a pet.
這是暴風
This is Storm.
他從前與海王並肩戰鬥
He's fought alongside Aquaman before,
所以他總是願意伸出援手
so he's always ready to lend a hand.
或者是援鰭 哈？
Or a fin. Huh?
諸位？
Guys?
超人 保持超級
Superman, stay super.
暴風 我們需要你帶我們下海
Storm, we'll need you to lead us out to sea
穿過你來時經過的海底隧道
through the ocean tunnel you came from.
但首先 我們需要個交通工具
But first,we'll need a vehicle.
潛水艇怎麼樣？
How about a sub?
搞懂笑點沒？一個潛水艇三明治 哈哈哈
Get it?A submarine sandwich.
抱歉……那個可以用
- Sorry...- That'll work.
又來了
Aw! Not again.
一個超級大小的潛水艇準備行動
One supersized sub ready for action.
諸位！我們走吧，超人！
- Guys!- Let's go, Superman.
是啊 你在那裡擋啥呢？
Yeah, what's the hold-up?
清除 清除
Eliminate. Eliminate.
清除……哦，多可愛的小房間吶
Eliminate...Oh, my, what a lovely room.
暴風 去蝙蝠洞
Storm, to the Batcave.
“星球日報”
The Daily Planet,
很快就要被更名為逆閃星球了
soon to be renamed the Reverse-Flash Planet.
還有這個完美的天線
And the perfect antenna
可以把我的個人宣言廣播到世界的每一個角落
to broadcast my manifesto across the world!
你們好啊 地球！
Hello, planet Earth!
是我 一直以來最受喜愛的超級英雄
It's me, the most beloved superhero of all time,
逆閃電
Reverse-Flash.
哦！
Ooh!
逆閃電呀 我超愛他的
The Reverse-Flash.I love him.
現在 我已經打破了充滿罪惡的舊世界
Now that I've rid the world of crime,
我覺得是你們回報一下老逆閃的時候了
I think it's time for you to repay old R.F.
因為他仁慈的慷慨
for his kind generosity.
所以我命令每一個人都要到
That's why I'm ordering everyone to report
我的逆閃電指揮中心來向我匯報
to my Reverse-Flash command centers.
在那裡 你們會接到指示 由我 你們的新主宰者
There, you'll be given orders on what I, your new ruler,
告訴你們我想讓你們做什麼 聽起來是不是很棒？
would like you to do.Doesn't that sound wonderful?
沒教養的猴崽子 我早就知道他不安好心
Cheeky monkey, I always knew he was rotten.
現在趕緊的！
Now hurry!
你們不想讓我像對付正義聯盟一樣
You don't want what I did to the Justice League
對付你們吧
to happen to you.
他的能力提升了以後 我們中的任何人都不是他的對手了
With his increased powers, none of us are any match for him.
哦！我到處找你們大家 現在聽我說
Ah! I've been looking everywhere for you guys. Now listen,
我知道你們多半還在為那些惡作劇生我的氣
I know you're probably still mad at me for those pranks,
但是問題是 它不是我幹的
but the thing is,it wasn't me.
它是這個騙人 邪惡 下流的
It was this cheating,evil, dirty,
長著一張蠢臉的冒名頂替的傢伙乾的 他從未來穿越回來的 名字叫……
doofus-faced imposter from the future named...
逆閃電
Reverse-Flash.
等下 你們知道他在冒充我？
Wait. You knew he was impersonating me?
不 我們不知道 一開始不知道
No, we didn't.Not at first.
但是有三條線索
But there were three clues.
你神秘兮兮的時間循環麻煩
Your mysterious time loop trouble.
你對孩子式幼稚的惡作劇突如其來的興趣
Your sudden interest in childish pranks.
對我們說起的惡作劇矢口否認，又喪失了超能力
A sudden denial of said pranks and loss of powers.
你不同尋常的行為舉止讓我相信通過某種方法
Your unusual behavior patterns led me to believe that somehow,
某種途徑 某個人 某個地方
some way, someone,somewhere,
為了某個不可告人的目的陷害你
was framing you for some unknown purpose.
所以 你炒我魷魚是為了引出逆閃？
So, you fired me to flush out the Reverse-Flash?
一點也不錯 蝙蝠俠早就知道
Exactly.Batman knew that
一旦他達到了他的邪惡目的
once he accomplished his evil goals
他就會自己暴露大家面前
he'd reveal himself to you.
所以當他自曝身份的時候我就在那裡
That's why I was gonna be there when he did.
我縮小以後落在你的肩膀上
I shrunk down onto your shoulder
本打算回來向聯盟報告
and was going to report back to the League
但是反閃的手銬害我電路短路了
until Reverse-Flash's shackle shorted out my circuits,
所以我一直困在縮小模式裡
which kept me stuck in shrink mode.
那就是說你們從來沒有真正的放棄我
Then that means you guys never really gave up on me.
當然沒有啦
Of course not.
我們是超級夥伴嘛 夥計
We're superfriends, man.
騙了你真是非常對不起 閃電俠
We were sorry to deceive you, Flash.
我們只有這一個辦法幫你擺脫麻煩
It was our only play to get you out of trouble.
謝謝你們 這裡的每一個人
Thank you, everyone.
是啊 真是暖心一刻啊
Yeah, yeah,real heartwarming.
現在 輪到我幫大家擺脫麻煩了
And now, it's my turn to get us all out of trouble.
我們可以用這些來阻止逆閃
We can stop the Reverse-Flash with these.
神速磚
Speed Force bricks.
而且我們可以用我神速車上的這些磚
And we can use the bricks from my speed machine
來給我們其它的交通工具充滿能量
to superpower our other vehicles.
給我們所有人足夠快的速度來追上逆閃
Giving us all enough speed to keep up with Reverse-Flash.
嗯 我還沒拿回我的超能力呢 神奇女俠
Well, I don't have my speed powers back yet, Wonder Woman,
但是我有個更好的東西
but I have something better.
我有一個計劃
I have a plan.
告訴他們所有人 你們今天建造的地標
Tell them all, the landmarks you build today
將會使我的英名萬古長青
will glorify my name tomorrow and for all eternity.
看吶 是正義聯盟
Look, it's the Justice League!
歷史將銘記 世界上速度最快的人永遠都是……
History will know the fastest man alive was always...
萬歲!
Hurray!
嗨 你們大家！我們不打算退休了！
Hey, everybody!We're not retired anymore!
正義聯盟回歸
The Justice League is back.
黑暗騎士歸來
- And the Dark Knight returns. - Bark.
這麼說你們從正義大廳裡逃出來了
So you've escaped the Hall of Justice
你們的寵物們幫的忙 毫無疑問
with help from your pets,no doubt.
我希望你們能享受此刻的自由
I hope you enjoyed your freedom,
因為它將是你們臨終前看到的最後一件事了
because it will be the last thing you ever see.
神速磚能量開啟
Powering on the speed bricks.
哦哦 癢癢的！
Tickles!
哇啊！看那邊！
Whoa! Look at that!
看起來好像一切都靜止了
It looks like everything just stopped.
怪不得閃電俠總是動作那麼快
No wonder the Flash is always moving so fast.
生活在這麼一個慢吞吞的世界裡肯定很無聊
It must be boring to live in a world going so slow.
如果我們早知道他的世界是這樣的
If we'd known it was like this,
那我們真該對他再耐心點
we might have been more patient with him.
學到了寶貴的一課 隊員們 打起精神來
Lesson learned, team.Look alive.
你用什麼辦法獲得了神速力？
Somehow you've gained the power of the Speed Force.
不要緊 我還是比你們所有人都要快
No matter. I'm still faster than all of you.
調虎離山 散開！
Evasive maneuvers.Split up.
你們仍然不是神速力之核的對手
You're still no match for the nexus.
我動作可以快到可以
I can move so fast I can seem to be
同時出現在五個地方
in five different places at the same time.
而且我可以搞定你們所有人 一勞永逸！
And I can take care of all of you, once and for all!
- 準備好了嗎 大B？- 當然
- Ready, B'dg?- You bet.
我的神速磚正在返回神速力之地
My bricks are returning to the Speed Force Zone!
不！
No!
看起來閃電俠是對的
Looks like the Flash was right.
神速磚給了我們的飛行器
The speed bricks have given our vehicles
摧毀這些雕像的能力
the ability to destroy those statues.
拿下它 夥計們！
Go get 'em, gang!
目標鎖定 開火！
- Target locked.- Fire!
炸沒嘍！
It's away!
不！
No!
我不知道你那些神速磚是怎麼得來的
I don't know how you got those speed bricks
但是你的計劃失敗了
but your plan failed.
我的力量強大到
I'm powerful enough
不管你們在哪 都能擊敗正義聯盟
to beat the Justice League,no matter where you are!
我們可沒打算跟你打
We weren't trying to beat you.
我們只是想分散你的注意力
We were trying to distract you.
什麼？
What?
這不可能 你是怎麼……
Impossible. How did you...
在神速力之地的那些考驗
The trials in the Speed Force Zone
不只是為了看看我是不是夠資格
weren't just there to see if I was worthy,
那些考驗是為了教導我一些東西
they were there to teach me something.
一些如果你花點時間自己去通關就會搞明白的事
Something you would have known if you took the time to go through them.
說夠了吧！
Enough of this!
我身上還有足夠的神速之核的能量
I still have enough of the nexus energy
可以打敗像你這樣的人
to defeat the likes of you.
好強的力量！
So much power!
這些力量本該是我的才對！
Which is rightfully mine!
我出現在你面前之前 你根本都不知道神速力是什麼
You didn't even know what the Speed Force was until I showed up.
你憑什麼以為你現在知道得足夠多可以打敗我？
What makes you think you know enough about it now to defeat me?
只有一個辦法能找出答案了
Only one way to find out.
你永遠打不贏我的 閃電俠
You'll never beat me, Flash.
我才是掌握了神速力的大師
I'm the master of the Speed Force!
真的嗎？一個大師級人物應該有個計劃的吧？
Really? Wouldn't a master have a plan
所以他沒被絆倒啊？
so he doesn't get tripped up?
我猜是沒有
Guess not.
你看起來很累嘛 也許你應該放慢速度
You're looking tired. Maybe you should slow down.
- 不！- 好啊
- No!- Okay.
什麼？
What?
很疼 對吧？
- Hurts, doesn't it?- Huh?
留意周圍 神速力大師
Way to be aware of your surroundings, Speed Force master.
也許你今天會贏
You may have won today,
但是我可以回到過去
but I'll travel back in time
阻止你拿到神速力之核
and stop you from getting the nexus.
我覺得你已經沒有足夠的力量了 逆閃
I don't think you have enough steam, R.F.
看起來你最後的神速力核之力也用完了
It looks like the last of the nexus energy is gone.
沒有它 你根本就不夠快
Without it,you're just not fast enough.
不夠快？我是世界上速度最快的人！
Fast enough?I'm the fastest man alive!
就是我！
I am!
證明給我看
Prove it.
快點啊 逆閃
- Come on, R.F.- Huh?
你可以跑得更快的
You can go faster than that.
真的嗎？你就這點本事了？
Really? That's all you've got?
什麼？
What?
手銬不可能鎖得住我
Handcuffs can't hold me.
我只要……
All I have to do is...
怎麼回事？
Huh? What?
我的超能力
My powers.
嘖嘖嘖 看起來有人和神速力之間的連接斷掉了
Uh-uh-uh. Looks like someone broke his connection to the Speed Force.
嘖嘖
Tsk, tsk.
你應該放慢速度
You should have slowed down.
你 你騙我！
You! You tricked me!
我只是執行我的計劃而已
No, no.I just executed my plan.
你跑不了的！
You won't get away with this!
我會回來的！
I'll come back!
不好意思 你講話這麼慢我聽不懂你在說什麼
Sorry. I... I can't understand when you're talking so slow.
媽媽
Mummy.
嗯 我們不會有什麼麻煩事兒了
Well, we won't have any trouble
逆閃出事以後能消停好一陣子
from Reverse-Flash for a while.
- 那個神速之核怎麼辦？- 什麼怎麼辦？
- What about the nexus thingy?- What about it?
擁有那樣的力量
With power like that,
你可以把從此以後所有的超級英雄的活都乾了
you could do the job of every hero forever.
看起來正義聯盟還是在退休狀態啊
Looks like the Justice League is still retired.
不
No.
沒人應該擁有這樣的力量
No one should have this much power.
你……
You...
你放棄了那樣的力量
You gave up all that speed.
為什麼呢？
But why?
嗯 最後我發現放慢速度
Well, it turns out that slowing down
才是打敗逆閃的最佳途徑
was the best way to defeat Reverse-Flash.
神速力之核的力量讓他不能集中精神
The nexus power had him so distracted,
他完全忽視了自己周圍的一切
he was totally unaware of his surroundings.
我絕對不能讓那樣的事發生在我身上
No way would I ever let that happen to me.
歸還神速之核的力量一直就是我計劃的……一部分
Returning the nexus was always a part of my... plan,
而且這些也是你們大家一直想要教導我的事
and these were all the things you guys were trying to teach me.
謝謝大家
Thank you.
要不是有你們這樣的朋友，我將會永遠失去我的超能力
Without friends like you, I would have lost my powers forever.
而我們也得被迫永久退休了
And we would have been retired forever.
這倒提醒我了
That reminds me,
我們正義聯盟有沒有什麼養老金計劃或者……
is there a Justice League pension plan or...
你回來真是太好了 閃電俠
It's good to have you back, Flash.
還有了你新得到的智慧的引導
And with newfound wisdom to guide you.
也許是這樣 神奇女俠
That may be true,Wonder Woman,
但閃電俠才剛剛證明了
but Flash has only proven
他已經為下一階段的特訓做好準備了
he's ready for the next level of training.
現在開始真正的考驗的是
Now begins the true test
閃電俠精神上的敏銳和不屈不撓
of Flash's mental acuity and fortitude.
我準備的考驗異常殘酷
The training crucible I have prepared
將摧毀他隱藏在內心的軟弱
will destroy hidden weakness
鍛煉出內心所需要的強大的力量來……
and forge the inner strength required to...
唔 聽起來很棒 蝙蝠俠
Hmm. It sounds great, Batman.
我們開始吧
Let's get started on that.
吃完小點心再開始
Right after a little snack.
神速力之核已經被送回了神速力之地
The nexus has been returned to the Speed Force.
宇宙已經重獲秩序
And order has been restored to the universe.
所有這些只用了……
And all it took was...
魔力呀 寶貝 只是一點小小的魔力
? Magic, baby It's just a little magic ?
- 扎塔娜 - 起不對……
- Zatanna.- Yrros.